Subtitle Provide by dramacool.in Translator [Admin.@YNG]
تم توفير الترجمة بواسطة مترجم dramacool.in [Admin.@YNG]
Xu Xin
شو شين
Renowned artist Lu Ming and his wife were in a car accident.
تعرض الفنان الشهير لو مينغ وزوجته لحادث سيارة.
Lu Ming is now out of danger.
لو مينغ أصبح الآن خارج الخطر.
His wife remains in a coma.
وتظل زوجته في غيبوبة.
The cause of the accident is still under investigation.
ولا يزال سبب الحادث قيد التحقيق.
Xu Xin
شو شين
Can you hear me?
أيمكنك سماعي؟
What happened that day was fate.
ما حدث في ذلك اليوم كان قدرا.
Maybe it doesn't want us to be apart.
ربما لا يريدنا أن نكون منفصلين.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I'll always be by your side.
سوف أكون بجانبك دائمًا.
Always, no matter what.
دائما، مهما كان الأمر.
Doctor.
طبيب.
Please tell me honestly.
من فضلك قل لي بصراحة.
What's Xu Xin's condition right now?
ما هي حالة Xu Xin الآن؟
Why hasn't she woken up?
لماذا لم تستيقظ؟
Your wife's external injuries aren't very serious.
إن الإصابات الخارجية التي أصيبت بها زوجتك ليست خطيرة جدًا.
She should recover from those soon.
ينبغي لها أن تتعافى من تلك قريبا.
But she's still unconscious.
لكنها لا تزال فاقدة للوعي.
That's because her head injury is more complicated.
وذلك لأن إصابة رأسها أكثر تعقيدًا.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
Her head
رأسها
was severely hit in the accident.
أصيب بجروح بالغة في الحادث.
It's not life-threatening,
إنه ليس مهددا للحياة،
but it may be pressing on certain nerves.
ولكن قد يكون ذلك ضغطًا على أعصاب معينة.
This has caused brain damage.
وقد تسبب هذا في تلف في الدماغ.
And this damage is irreversible.
وهذا الضرر لا يمكن إصلاحه.
Irreversible?
لا رجعة فيه؟
Yes.
نعم.
What will happen as a result?
ماذا سيحدث نتيجة لذلك؟
Long-term vascular compression
الضغط الوعائي طويل الأمد
can affect normal brain function.
يمكن أن يؤثر على وظائف المخ الطبيعية.
This mainly leads to cognitive decline,
وهذا يؤدي بشكل رئيسي إلى التدهور المعرفي،
reduced intelligence,
انخفاض الذكاء،
and emotional instability.
وعدم الاستقرار العاطفي.
Her condition may be more complicated than I thought.
ربما تكون حالتها أكثر تعقيدًا مما كنت أعتقد.
But please don't worry.
ولكن من فضلك لا تقلق.
Our hospital's medical equipment
المعدات الطبية في مستشفانا
is already the most advanced.
هو بالفعل الأكثر تقدما.
Your wife is in the best ward.
زوجتك في أفضل حال.
She has access to the most advanced equipment 24/7.
يمكنها الوصول إلى أحدث المعدات على مدار الساعة طوال أيام الأسبوع.
She's under constant monitoring.
إنها تحت المراقبة المستمرة.
As for when she'll wake up,
أما بالنسبة لموعد استيقاظها،
it depends on her own willpower.
فالأمر يعتمد على إرادتها الخاصة.
Because everyone's situation is different.
لأن وضع كل شخص يختلف.
Then what should we do?
إذن ماذا يجب علينا أن نفعل؟
Also,
أيضًا،
family support is very important.
دعم الأسرة مهم جدًا.
Spend more time with her.
اقضي المزيد من الوقت معها.
Sir,
سيد،
Would you like to go back and get some rest?
هل ترغب بالعودة والحصول على بعض الراحة؟
You've been here for several days now.
لقد كنت هنا منذ عدة أيام الآن.
Your body can't take it.
جسدك لا يستطيع تحمل ذلك.
No need.
لا حاجة.
I'll stay here with her.
سأبقى هنا معها.
I feel more at ease watching over her.
أشعر براحة أكبر عندما أراقبها.
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
I'll go home tomorrow to get something.
سأذهب إلى المنزل غدًا لأحصل على شيء ما.
Thank you for taking care of her.
شكرا لك على رعايتها.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
This is your favorite dress.
هذا هو فستانك المفضل.
I brought it for you.
لقد أحضرته لك.
When you wake up,
عندما تستيقظ،
let's put it on and dance, okay?
دعونا نضعها ونرقص، حسنًا؟
I know you can hear me.
أعلم أنك تستطيع أن تسمعني.
You're just tired.
أنت متعب فقط.
You just want a good rest, right?
أنت تريد فقط راحة جيدة، أليس كذلك؟
In the past,
في الماضي،
you always said I didn't listen to you.
لقد قلت دائمًا أنني لم أستمع إليك.
When you wake up,
عندما تستيقظ،
I'll really listen to you.
سأستمع إليك حقا.
No matter what you say,
بغض النظر عما تقوله،
I'll listen carefully to every word.
سأستمع بعناية لكل كلمة.
Xu Xin opens her eyes and looks at Lu Ming beside her.
تفتح Xu Xin عينيها وتنظر إلى Lu Ming بجانبها.
He feels both familiar and strange.
إنه يشعر بأنه مألوف وغريب في نفس الوقت.
Dr. Xu Ran tells her
الدكتورة شو ران تخبرها
that everything she sees is a hallucination.
أن كل ما تراه هو هلوسة.
Yet the appearance of that man and child
ومع ذلك فإن ظهور ذلك الرجل والطفل
seems to tell her
يبدو أنه يخبرها
that all of this really happened.
أن كل هذا حدث بالفعل.
Every girl's disappearance
اختفاء كل فتاة
seems to be connected to her husband.
ويبدو أنها مرتبطة بزوجها.
And the only person in the world who believes her
والشخص الوحيد في العالم الذي يصدقها
is Yuan You.
هو يوان يو.
But what Xu Xin doesn't know
ولكن ما لا يعرفه Xu Xin
is that this man is the mastermind behind it all.
أن هذا الرجل هو العقل المدبر وراء كل هذا.
When Yuan You was very young,
عندما كان يوان يو صغيرًا جدًا،
his father often took him hunting in the mountains.
كان والده يأخذه في كثير من الأحيان للصيد في الجبال.
His father told him
قال له والده
everyone should have
ينبغي للجميع أن يكون لديهم
a little wooden cabin of their own.
كوخ خشبي صغير خاص بهم.
In Yuan You's cabin,
في كابينة يوان يو،
there was only an empty glass tank.
لم يكن هناك سوى خزان زجاجي فارغ.
This was Yuan You's secret alone.
كان هذا سر يوان يو وحده.
He would only share it with those closest to him.
كان يشاركها فقط مع أقرب الناس إليه.
But when someone learned the secret,
ولكن عندما علم أحدهم السر،
it was also the time they would leave Yuan You.
وكان هذا أيضًا هو الوقت الذي سيغادرون فيه يوان يو.
So Yuan You was both special and lonely.
لذا كان يوان يو مميزًا ووحيدًا.
The loneliness was so intense
لقد كان الشعور بالوحدة شديدا للغاية
it nearly consumed him.
لقد كاد أن يستهلكه.
Xu Xin's arrival
وصول شو شين
changed everything.
لقد تغير كل شيء.
At first, he was doubtful about this encounter.
في البداية، كان يشك في هذا اللقاء.
Until that incident happened.
حتى حدثت تلك الحادثة.
That night,
في تلك الليلة،
Yuan You had a dream that felt too real.
يوان لقد كان لديك حلم بدا حقيقيا للغاية.
In the dream, he stood before Xu Xin.
وفي الحلم، كان واقفا أمام شو شين.
But she ignored him completely.
لكنها تجاهلته تماما.
After that,
بعد ذلك،
Yuan You had a theory.
يوان لقد كان لديك نظرية.
A hope.
أمل.
He thought he had found
كان يعتقد أنه وجد
someone who would end his loneliness.
شخص ينهي وحدته.
Buying flowers for your girlfriend again?
شراء الزهور لصديقتك مرة أخرى؟
You two are really so loving.
انتم الاثنين محبين حقا.
Yes.
نعم.
They're for my beloved.
إنهم لحبيبي.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Ms. Xu, your flowers.
السيدة شو، زهورك.
In the dreams connected to Xu Xin,
في الأحلام المرتبطة بـ Xu Xin،
Yuan You got the information he needed.
يوان لقد حصلت على المعلومات التي يحتاجها.
He just needed one more confirmation.
كان يحتاج فقط إلى تأكيد آخر.
Yuan You was one step away from proving
كان يوان يو على بعد خطوة واحدة من الإثبات
he was no longer alone.
لم يعد وحيدا.
All it took was a necessary sacrifice.
كل ما تطلبه الأمر هو التضحية الضرورية.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Little Tangyuan drew a girl.
رسم تانغ يوان الصغير فتاة.
Maybe I've seen her in my dreams.
ربما رأيتها في أحلامي.
And so, Yuan You began his plan.
وهكذا بدأ يوان يو خطته.
He wanted Xu Xin all to himself.
لقد أراد أن يكون Xu Xin كله لنفسه.
Even if it meant destroying
حتى لو كان ذلك يعني التدمير
everything Xu Xin had.
كل ما كان لدى Xu Xin.
No one could stop him.
لم يتمكن أحد من إيقافه.
Because in Yuan You's world,
لأنه في عالم يوان يو،
everything he did
كل ما فعله
had the highest motive.
كان لديه الدافع الأعلى.
Called
مُسَمًّى
love.
حب.
Xu Xin,
شو شين,
when did you write this novel?
متى كتبت هذه الرواية؟
I remember back in college,
أتذكر في الكلية،
you said you loved literature.
قلت أنك تحب الأدب.
If you ever stopped dancing,
إذا توقفت عن الرقص يومًا ما،
you might try to become a novelist.
ربما تحاول أن تصبح روائيًا.
To write the stories you wanted.
لكتابة القصص التي تريدها.
What I didn't know
ما لم اعرفه
was that you actually did it.
هل كنت أنت من فعل ذلك فعلاً؟
Xu Xin,
شو شين,
how many more things
كم عدد الأشياء الأخرى
do I not know about you?
هل لا أعلم عنك؟
Please wake up soon, okay?
من فضلك استيقظ قريبا، حسنًا؟
Wake up.
استيقظ.
Tell me everything you want to say
أخبرني بكل ما تريد قوله
face to face, okay?
وجهاً لوجه، حسناً؟
I finally found you.
لقد وجدتك أخيرا.
Lao Lu,
لاو لو،
You can't be so negative.
لا يمكنك أن تكون سلبيا إلى هذه الدرجة.
No one knows when Xu Xin will wake up.
لا أحد يعلم متى سوف يستيقظ Xu Xin.
You'll need even more money in the future.
سوف تحتاج إلى المزيد من المال في المستقبل.
We have to keep going.
علينا أن نستمر.
Boss Ma said,
قال الرئيس ما،
You two as a couple should still promote yourselves.
يجب على كلاكما كزوجين أن تقوما بالترويج لأنفسكما.
That way,
بهذه الطريقة،
Even if people criticize you, it's not a loss.
حتى لو انتقدك الناس، فهذا ليس خسارة.
Being controversially famous is still fame.
إن كونك مشهورًا بشكل مثير للجدل لا يزال يعتبر شهرة.
Many artists don't have your advantages.
العديد من الفنانين لا يتمتعون بمزاياك.
You know that?
هل تعلم ذلك؟
Forget it.
انسى ذلك.
Yeah.
نعم.
What about them?
ماذا عنهم؟
If you want to let it go, then let it go.
إذا كنت تريد أن تتركه، فاتركه.
But who are you?
ولكن من أنت؟
You're Lu Ming.
أنت لو مينغ.
Xu Ran.
شو ران.
I mean, let's end things between us.
أعني، دعونا ننهي الأمور بيننا.
When everything is over,
عندما ينتهي كل شيء،
I don't want to get involved anymore.
لا أريد أن أتدخل بعد الآن.
No,
لا،
Lao Lu, did I hear you right?
لاو لو، هل سمعتك بشكل صحيح؟
You're giving up all this money?
هل تتنازل عن كل هذه الأموال؟
Do you have something against money?
هل لديك شيء ضد المال؟
Xu Xin's treatment needs money.
علاج Xu Xin يحتاج إلى المال.
I can sell my house and patents.
أستطيع أن أبيع منزلي وبراءات الاختراع الخاصة بي.
I'll sell everything valuable I own.
سأبيع كل ما أملكه من أشياء ثمينة.
I don't care.
لا أهتم.
No,
لا،
With that attitude,
مع هذا الموقف،
Why don't we try harder?
لماذا لا نحاول بجهد أكبر؟
Let's make a comeback.
دعونا نعود.
You don't understand how much Xu Xin means to me.
أنت لا تفهم كم يعني لي Xu Xin.
She's so important.
إنها مهمة جدًا.
She's done so much for me.
لقد فعلت الكثير من أجلي.
But I've only been taking from her.
ولكنني كنت آخذ منها فقط.
That was never my intention.
لم يكن هذا قصدي أبدًا.
At the beginning,
في البداية،
I just wanted to give her a better life.
أردت فقط أن أمنحها حياة أفضل.
To prove myself to her family.
لأثبت نفسي لعائلتها.
Now it all seems ridiculous.
الآن يبدو الأمر كله سخيفًا.
I'm afraid of losing her,
أنا خائف من فقدانها
but I keep pushing her away.
لكنني أستمر في دفعها بعيدًا.
Now she's lying there.
الآن هي مستلقية هناك.
To her,
لها،
I'm just the one who hurt her.
أنا فقط من أذيتها.
Do you understand?
هل تفهم؟
But
لكن
What if she never wakes up?
ماذا لو لم تستيقظ أبدًا؟
Will you regret it?
هل ستندم على ذلك؟
I will regret it.
سوف أندم على ذلك.
In the name of love,
باسم الحب
I've been hurting her all along.
لقد كنت أؤذيها طوال الوقت.
I'll wait for her to wake up.
سأنتظرها حتى تستيقظ.
After she wakes up,
بعد أن تستيقظ،
I'll let her choose the life she wants.
سأتركها تختار الحياة التي تريدها.
That's the greatest relief for her.
هذا هو أعظم ارتياح لها.
I understand.
أفهم.
Lao Lu,
لاو لو،
You're my brother.
أنت أخي.
Whatever you choose,
مهما كان اختيارك،
I respect you.
انا احترمك.
Take care of yourself.
اعتنِ بنفسك.
What about you?
ماذا عنك؟
What are you going to do next?
ماذا ستفعل بعد ذلك؟
Xu Xin wrote a novel.
شو شين كتب رواية.
For a while,
لفترة من الوقت،
she often went to a bookstore to write.
كانت تذهب إلى المكتبة كثيرًا للكتابة.
I want to go there and see.
أريد أن أذهب إلى هناك وأرى.
To really try to understand her.
لمحاولة فهمها حقًا.
I know Miss Xu Xin.
انا اعرف الانسة شو شين.
She works there every weekend.
إنها تعمل هناك في نهاية كل أسبوع.
Yuan You step by step
يوان يو خطوة بخطوة
led Xu Xin to Lu Ming.
قاد Xu Xin إلى Lu Ming.
But at the last moment,
ولكن في اللحظة الأخيرة،
he slipped up.
لقد انزلق.
I don't think I've ever told you
لا أعتقد أنني أخبرتك من قبل
that girl was wearing red, right?
كانت تلك الفتاة ترتدي اللون الأحمر، أليس كذلك؟
Yuan You.
يوان يو.
Let go.
اتركه.
Why are you doing this to me?
لماذا تفعل بي هذا؟
I've done so much for you.
لقد فعلت الكثير من أجلك.
Why don't you trust me?
لماذا لا تثق بي؟
Why?
لماذا؟
Yuan You's grip tightened.
تشدّدت قبضة يوان يو.
He watched helplessly
لقد شاهد بعجز
as the light faded from Xu Xin's eyes.
كما تلاشى الضوء من عيون Xu Xin.
At that moment,
في تلك اللحظة،
memories flashed through his mind—
ذكريات تومض في ذهنه؟؟؟
the first time he met Xu Xin.
المرة الأولى التي التقى فيها بـ Xu Xin.
Xu Xin, Xu Xin, Xu Xin...
شو شين، شو شين، شو شين...
It was you.
لقد كنت أنت.
All along,
طوال الوقت،
it was always you.
لقد كنت أنت دائما.
Always you.
دائما انت.
Yes, it was me.
نعم لقد كنت انا.
I did it all.
لقد فعلت كل ذلك.
Xu Xin, you wouldn't understand.
شو شين، أنت لن تفهم.
Everything I did was because of you.
كل ما فعلته كان بفضلك.
All because of you.
كل هذا بفضلك.
Because of us.
بسببنا.
Because I love you.
لاننى احبك.
No one loves you more than I do.
لا أحد يحبك أكثر مني.
And you love me too, don't you?
وأنت تحبني أيضًا، أليس كذلك؟
Otherwise, why would you
وإلا فلماذا تفعل ذلك؟
do those things to me?
هل تفعل هذه الأشياء بي؟
You kept coming into my room.
كنت تستمر في المجيء إلى غرفتي.
You kissed me first.
لقد قبلتني أولاً.
What did I
ماذا فعلت
ever do to you?
ماذا تفعل لك من قبل؟
Yuan You.
يوان يو.
I've never kissed you.
لم أقبلك أبدًا.
How did this crazy woman get here?
كيف وصلت هذه المرأة المجنونة إلى هنا؟
Why are you here?
لماذا انت هنا؟
What are you talking about?
ماذا تتحدث عنه؟
Are you too tired?
هل أنت متعب جداً؟
Don't touch me.
لا تلمسني.
If you're not in the mood,
إذا لم تكن في مزاج جيد،
I'll just go back to my room.
سأعود إلى غرفتي.
Xu Xin.
شو شين.
I told you, you can call me Xu Xin.
لقد قلت لك، يمكنك أن تناديني بـ Xu Xin.
Get out.
اخرج.
I told you, you can pretend I'm someone else.
لقد قلت لك، يمكنك التظاهر بأنني شخص آخر.
But Yuan You,
لكن يوان يو،
I really think you're sick.
أعتقد حقا أنك مريض.
You need to see a doctor.
يجب عليك رؤية الطبيب.
Xu Xin.
شو شين.
I know there's still distance between us.
أعلم أن المسافة لا تزال بيننا.
But just now,
ولكن الآن فقط،
I really wanted to kill you.
لقد أردت قتلك حقا.
I don't know what else I can do.
لا أعلم ماذا يمكنني أن أفعل غير ذلك.
I've done everything I could.
لقد فعلت كل ما بوسعي.
Not every effort
ليس كل جهد
will be met with love.
سيتم استقباله بالحب.
Xu Xin
شو شين
Your novel stops abruptly at this point.
توقفت روايتك فجأة عند هذه النقطة.
Clearly, you haven't
من الواضح أنك لم تفعل
had the chance to put a period at the end.
أتيحت لي الفرصة لوضع نقطة في النهاية.
Why did you write a novel like this?
لماذا كتبت رواية كهذه؟
I have a feeling
لدي شعور
that everything about us is hidden in this story.
أن كل شيء عنا مخفي في هذه القصة.
Let me return to where it all began.
دعوني أعود إلى حيث بدأ كل شيء.
To see the truth behind everything.
لرؤية الحقيقة وراء كل شيء.
Excuse me, student.
عذرا يا طالب.
I remember your name is Lu Ming, right?
أتذكر أن اسمك هو لو مينغ، أليس كذلك؟
Yes.
نعم.